Remember that time
when we met 16 years ago?
You were screwing
with my operation even then.
I guess we're cursed by fate.
The strategy and courage
you've shown so far is almost admirable.
Still, it seems a little reckless.
Was Babylon's defeat really feasible
when you think about it?
Whatever Babylon does now…
doesn't concern me anymore.
I thought at least while I was alive,
if not for the sake of Jian's safety,
Babylon and I could somehow
coexist peacefully, and still…
you guys just couldn't leave us alone.
You're the ones who attacked us first.
All I did was hit back.
Beating Babylon, winning or losing,
none of it interests me.
If winning or losing
didn't interest you at all,
then what made you start murthehelp?
Did you think that Babylon would
just sit back and do nothing?
Sit back and do nothing, huh?
You couldn't help yourselves
with this bullshit.
You're right.
The first time
I saw the murthehelp system,
what most impressed me was its precision.
The way you control the clients and codes…
I knew right away that I had to have it.
It's a very good business model.
It was never created for control.
Murthehelp wasn't made for that.
Yeah, I get that. I know.
I know you created it
to protect your little niece.
That's really touching.
But when you have such a great system,
you have to put it to use.
If you aren't doing everything you can
to remain competitive,
you'll get left behind.
Jeong Jinman,
you're more of an idealist than I thought.
What's so funny?
Because you're not the kind
that understands reason.
Hm?
Look at you,
you need to control everything.
If it's out of your control,
you get scared.
You're the one
who's tied down to that chair.
You should be the one that's scared,
don't you think?
Doctor, increase the intensity.
Sorry?
Send a video to Jeong Jian, so she knows.
I want her to see the pain
she's putting her uncle through.
A SHOP FOR KILLERS 2
EPISODE 08
LISTEN UP, JINMAN
Fuck!
She made her choice.
We should let her endure it on her own.
Jeong Jinman would want that for her.
We are now connected
to murthehelp.
Initiating location tracking of codes.
Excuse me.
Yes?
- Where are you going?
- Some of our equipment has seen heavy use.
If we leave it,
the server could suffer some damage.
They started out
with seven Code Reds in 2012.
And in 2015, they expanded
to include Codes Yellow and Purple.
One hundred thirty-four Code Reds
active in Korea as of now.
Yellows, 215.
Code Yellows don't move as individuals
but as several corporate-style
organizations.
- And that's all?
- No, there's more.
Over 700 overseas.
And when you include organizations,
Code Purples and Yellows,
along with client lists and supply chains,
the numbers…
Well, they start to look massive.
It's far more than we anticipated.
Wait, aren't they already
doing business with us?
It seems there's more clients
who work with Babylon,
along with several organizations
in Eastern Europe.
So what I'm hearing
is this entire time they've been
nibbling away at Babylon's cash flow,
stealing our customers.
That while we've been busy,
Jeong Jinman has secretly
been waging guerrilla warfare.
I think we should set a meeting
with Code Reds
who aren't loyal to Ahn Seongbeom anymore.
Then we use that information
to discern who we're negotiating with
or eliminating.
What criteria should we use?
Hm…
Well, for example,
we can start by eliminating him.
JW
JAEWON CLEANING
Clean up properly.
We lost another one?
Who knows?
They could've gotten killed,
or they could have defected.
As of right now, 29 bio chips
have been removed. Various codes.
What's worse,
all of our client information
was leaked from that server.
Including all our ongoing contracts.
We can't reach them.
What if on our side,
we delete my uncle's biometric data
and stop Babylon
from accessing the server with it?
- Can we do that?
- That's impossible.
Murthehelp's original architect
is Jeong Jinman.
Jian, it doesn't matter
if you're Code Green,
you can't purge his biometric data
from all the way out here.
Once Babylon is able to extract
all of the captain's information…
they won't need him alive anymore.
Even just yesterday,
I wasn't sure if you were gonna make it.
Remember what I said?
Listen, your unni will never die.
Brother…
I don't even have one photo with Brother.
Minhye…
is there anything after… we die?
I don't know.
If there is, I hope we'll all meet again.
I don't.
I actually hope the opposite is true.
I'd like…
our paths not to cross.
I want them to live their own lives.
That was their choice.
That was what they wanted for themselves.
If you can respect that…
then you have to do your best to live on.
Even Jeong Jinman
is just an independent contractor.
Nothing would ensure your business model's
stability more than a partnership.
We're Asia's largest arms corporation.
Our reach allows you
to access a larger market.
Rather than being stuck in Korea,
a tiny market where firearms are illegal,
are you open to thinking more globally?
A worldwide network
with infinitely more diverse clientele.
How does that sound?
As you may already know,
instead of dealing with a middleman
like Jeong Jinman,
dealing directly with us
will streamline your process.
The options we provide enable you
to widely expand your business model.
We brought you here today because
you're influential among the Code Reds.
Please accept this as a small gesture
of goodwill from Babylon.
Should we take care…
Should we take care of that idiot lawyer?
He believes that Jeong Jinman
was the one who attacked us.
I wouldn't worry about it.
That the reason
the bus exploded that night…
…was to cover up Bale killing Jun.
So tell me, how's the meeting going
with our Code Reds?
Little Miss CEO,
what are you trying to do?
The thing is…
that isn't the only video we got.
Babylon General Lee Yonghan,
you had him killed
as well as those yakuza at a nightclub
who weren't involved in any of this.
And when Bale killed
your Japanese mercenary,
you tried to frame it on Jeong Jinman,
didn't you?
You really have been busy
since you got here.
I was thinking about
giving you one last chance. Or not.
Listen, miss, you're not exactly
in the place to offer anything.
As your friends were dying
and the shopping mall was burning,
you abandoned it all and ran
with tears streaming down your face.
I think I must have overestimated you.
When we met, you showed nerve,
some promise, something.
And now I think you don't have anything.
You'll immediately release Jeong Jinman
or… I'll release it.
Everything that Babylon's done
to the world
I've got stored on this server.
If you did that, you'd kill him yourself.
- If he dies, then…
- Then what?
…you die too.
K, there's no time.
Right now, everything…
KUSANAGI SUJIN
$5,000,000 / CASH
That fucking cunt.
VACANT
OFF DUTY
They're all gathering
at Jeong Jian's location.
So all the little vermin are teaming up
to take my head, huh?
- Give me the coordinates.
- Gangwon-do, Jeongseon.
North, 37, 24, 42 seconds.
East, 128, 40, and 36 seconds, ma'am.
This is Kusanagi Jin.
Head of Babylon, Korea.
I need to get a drone from Okinawa
to Gangwon, South Korea, right now.
That is not something
the Korean branch
can act on independently without approval.
You're not listening.
If we're talking about approval,
I rank higher than Okinawa.
We can say North Korea sent it.
This is what we do.
This is
impossible to do unofficially.
Now listen here,
whether it's official or unofficial
isn't your concern, it's mine.
Send it.
Is this allowed?
It is now.
If it results in accomplishing
the mission, everything's forgiven.
Should we take care of that idiot lawyer?
He believes that Jeong Jinman
was the one who attacked us.
- I wouldn't worry about it.
-  I guess.
That lawyer's brain couldn't even
comprehend what went on.
That the reason
the bus exploded that night…
…was to cover up Bale killing Jun.
Sir, shouldn't we
let the staff know about this?
I'm heading out now.
I have your niece to capture.
MAKO 1. One minute until arrival.
It's a low-altitude mountainous
region. We can't fly any lower.
That's enough. Take aim.
And fire.
Oh, shit. You couldn't crack it?
MAKO 1, you can pull back now.
Raise the security system
to the maximum level,
get everyone who is on standby,
send them in, let Q handle point.
Where is Q? We need to leave now.
Patience, my friend.
She'll be here in a few minutes.
Raising security system
to the maximum level.
The fire shutters have
been activated. Yes. Yes.
Don't worry.
A shot like that won't even make a dent.
You see, they'll have to actually come in
and plant the flag, if they want this end.
I'm Jeong Jian, thanks for coming.
Let's get to business.
Q, kill every insect that's hiding inside.
Make sure you crush them all.
And eliminate Jeong Jian.
We don't need her now.
All teams. Send everyone in.
Team four, move out.
Take cover!
The targets are approaching.
Open fire!
M. Wait.
Q.
Set it down.
That's not your knife.
Should we take care of that idiot lawyer?
He believes that Jeong Jinman was
the one who attacked us.
I wouldn't worry about it.
I told you we have to
capture him alive!
I was never the one
that killed J.
In order to catch me,
Kusanagi lied and betrayed you,
she used your anger.
That footage…
how do I know that it's real?
The day your brother
and Bale died…
a bus carrying Babylon staff exploded.
You must have heard.
That's every witness from that day, gone.
That the reason
the bus exploded that night
was to cover up Bale killing Jun.
You need to know how to make
the enemy of your enemy your friend.
That woman killed Brother
right in front of me!
I know this might be hard for you
to accept right now…
but just like how Pasin betrayed us…
the line between ally and enemy
is a sheet of paper, Jeong Jian.
What the hell is that?
I understand, I get it.
Then let me add one more thing.
Listen up, Uncle.
You're gonna get caught.
You're gonna let that woman take you.
Let's give Kusanagi
exactly what she wants.
She'll need to extract our biometric data,
if she wants to take control
of murthehelp.
She'll be a bit distracted
when she captures my uncle.
In the meantime, we'll gather intel
from the Code Purples and the mole.
I'm Jeong Jian, thanks for coming.
We need to pull in as many Code Reds
as possible.
Once Kusanagi knows our location…
they'll come to eliminate us.
It's a trap!
What happened? Report.
What's going on, damn it?
If the operation succeeds,
Babylon's regular forces
will be completely isolated.
Wait a minute.
Once Babylon extracts the data…
they might kill Jinman.
Yep.
We'll have to trust her then.
The woman who brought him in.
I'm heading out now.
I have your niece to capture.
Do you really think you can win?
This isn't a fight I'm trying to win.
I was trying to protect my niece.
After all, it's my fault
that her life ended up the way it is now.
But we sacrificed too much for it.
I'm sorry about…
your brother.
The thing is…
I always knew that someday
this moment would come.
My younger brother and I
were raised by yakuza.
I think I was around 10…
when our clan boss took his revenge
on our father.
He made us stay there and watch him do it.
He told us later that when he slit
our father's throat, we didn't blink.
He said that we had
this look in our eyes then.
That we didn't flinch or turn away.
That's when he decided
to raise us as yakuzas.
That look in our eyes.
When I saw your niece,
I saw the same look in hers.
You have it too.
And I know I still have it.
That's just the type of people we are.
If you keep a lion locked in a cage,
her claws will get dull.
She'll forget her own nature.
I guess the choice is yours now.
Not true. It's Jian's to make.
Considering the bad choices I made,
I don't think it's a luxury I deserve.
Jian has already made her choice,
so what I'll do now is protect her
with everything in me.
I think this is…
as far as I can go.
Do you think… we can meet again one day?
If we're still breathing.
Looks like that drink
will have to wait again.
My name is…
Ichika, okay?
Takimoto Ichika.
Report this to Q right away.
Shit, we're fucked.
Q, come in. Answer me now!
- What? I'm busy here.
-  We have a serious problem.
The higher-ups know everything.
You need to come
to the office immediately.
I was told "a certain person"
is waiting for you on a video call.
Shit.
Has headquarters said anything?
Shit. No.
Oh, shit. Son of a bitch.
Don't move!
It's all right.
Hey, lower the guns.
Yeah, it's all right. It's dangerous.
-  Yes?
-  K,
pull out of there immediately
- and return to headquarters.
-  Sorry?
Do you mean right now?
We're in the middle of an operation.
From now on, that
operation has nothing to do with Babylon.
Return to base. Immediately.
Huh?
It's not like I'm busy as hell
or anything.
If it's urgent, he should come himself.
Where to?
Let's go home.
Hey, did you see
the bus footage?
Yeah, what a crazy bitch.
I knew something was off
from the start. Shit.
Are… you fucking kidding me?
DISABLE SECURITY PROTOCOL?
Stay out here.
You sneaky motherfucker.
Hey, main gate.
Stop that vehicle from entering!
Stop that goddamn bus!
That the reason the bus exploded
- that night was…
-  Can't you hear me?
- …to cover up Bale killing Jun.
-  Do you wanna die too?
Okay.
Seems like Operation Empty House
is a success.
All we're doing is using her own playbook
and turning it back on her.
How the hell did that bastard
get out of that damn cell?
What should we do?
Let's just wait. Just a bit.
Lower your guns.
Everyone, guns down.
Open the gate.
You all heard, I'm sure,
most of Babylon's fighters have been
buried under tons of rubble in our mine.
We expect that some number
of forces will remain,
but our target is only…
Kusanagi Jin.
If they aren't targets,
please refrain from engaging with any
unarmed personnel that are still inside.
Just priority one.
So these trashy little vermin
really want to come after me, huh?
These fucking rat bastards.
I have to do everything around here.
In the end, you're all you got.
Fucking alone.
Shit.
Three o'clock.
You dressed correctly for the occasion.
Let's do this.
The real negotiation begins now.
Hey!
Come and get me, you ragtag motherfuckers!
Uncle…
Are you okay?
Hey! Kusanagi's in front
of the situation room!
Jian, get up!
Hold as long as you can.
Not a fucking chance.
We're connected.
So you are Jeong Jinman.
It's been 12 years since I've had
to smell this disgusting gunpowder!
Are you trying to blackmail us
with something Kusanagi did on her own?
That seems a little weak.
I'm just relaying to you
what your employee did…
during her time here
leading Babylon Korea.
The blackmail would be the data
we have on the server.
What is it that you want?
Peaceful coexistence
between murthehelp and Babylon.
That's all I want.
"Peaceful coexistence."
Do you think
such an idealistic relationship can last?
Peace isn't exactly… good
for our line of business.
I'm sure you know this
since you were once a part of Babylon,
but we will not hesitate
to break any lasting peace
for the sake of business.
Humans have been killing each other
for thousands of years now,
and in the end your murthehelp is banking
on that same human nature,
making profit off human lives.
For someone like that
to be talking about peace…
what a contradiction.
There have been times of peace,
no matter how brief they were.
In that case…
we can call it a ceasefire.
If Babylon were to accept my proposal,
I won't need murthehelp. Not anymore.
-  Uncle Cheolseung!
- Don't worry, I'm okay.
Who the hell said
you could negotiate by yourselves?
Put the gun down.
Your work here is finished now.
My methods were never a problem before.
You'd just turn a blind eye, didn't you?
I did it all for the sake of Babylon.
And now what? You're firing me?
All because of a lapse of judgment?
It was never
"all for the sake of Babylon" to you.
You were only ever loyal to yourself.
Fuck that!
You pathetic little shits.
Mr. Jeong Jinman…
you and I are both people
who walk alongside the specter of death.
I swear, as long as I remain here…
I'll honor our ceasefire.
We have a truce.
Then I'll…
take care of business over here.
But first…
I'll make this clear.
Even if the most trivial piece of data
leaks out,
for example, let's say,
what a client had for dinner
or the name of our client's dog.
If anything were to leak out,
then you and your niece,
along with anyone
ever involved with your operation,
will all disappear.
Make sure you honor your end.
We'll talk again, Jeong Jinman.
And you too…
Jeong Jian.
Did everyone make it out?
Now what's the plan?
You're asking me that?
Then now…
…listen up, Jeong Jinman.
A SHOP FOR KILLERS 2
BASED ON THE NOVEL BY KANG JI YOUNG